// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "A loop becomes infinite loop if a condition never becomes ________",
    answer: "False",
    options: [
      "False",
      "True",
      "True or NULL",
      "NULL"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Python programming language allows to use one loop inside another loop known as?",
    answer: "Nested",
    options: [
      "switch",
      "Nested",
      "foreach",
      "forall"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Does python have switch case statement?",
    answer : "No",
    options: [
      "No",
      "Yes",
      "Python has switch statement but we can not use it.",
      "None of the mentioned"
      ]
      
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Can we write if/else into one line in python?",
    answer: "Yes",
    options: [
      "Yes",
      "No",
      "if/else not used in python",
      "None"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is an iteration in programming?",
    answer: "Steps counter",
    options: [
      "Variable",
      "Steps counter",
      "Fixed value",
      "Random value"
    ]
  },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "What will be output of this expression: 'p'+'q' if '12'.isdigit() else 'r'+'s'",
     answer: "pq",
     options: [
       "pq",
       "rs",
       "pqrs",
       "pq12"
     ]
   },
    {
     numb: 7,
     question: "The .......... construct allows to choose statements to be executed, depending upon the result of a condition.",
     answer: "selection",
     options: [
       "selection",
       "repetition",
       "sequence",
       "flow"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 8,
     question: "string = 'abcdef'         While z in string:        print(z, end=' ')",
     answer: "Error",
     options: [
       "a b c d e f",
       "abcdef",
       "Error",
       "None of these"
     ]
   },
  {
     numb: 9,
     question: "string = 'abcdef'     z = 'a'     while z in string:         print(z, end = ' ')",
     answer: "a a a a a....",
     options: [
       "z z z z....",
       "a a a a",
       "aaaa....",
       "a a a a a...."
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 10,
     question: "string = 'abcd'   for z in range(string):     print(z)",
     answer: "Error",
     options: [
       "abcd",
       "a b c d",
       "1 2 3 4 ",
       "Error"
     ]
   },
];